<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Losism]]></title>
  <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-06T13:31:47-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blakgeek.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[blakgeek]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Ma! I'm Blogging]]></title>
    <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/blog/2014/04/06/look-mom-im-blogging/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-06T12:46:56-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blakgeek.github.io/blog/2014/04/06/look-mom-im-blogging</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Losism aka &ldquo;The Way Of The Lost&rdquo; is a philosphical, no existential, nah a spiritual way of approaching software design and development.  It comes from the mind of a guy who is neither as smart nor hard working as many developers you will meet.  But do not judge the way of the Los just on those two facts, for Losism is a living, breathing, ever evolving thing much like the its creator.</p>

<p>There are two important things to be aware of as you embark on this journey.  One, Losism embraces typos but is willing to correct them.  So basically if you see a typo, missing word or something seems just generally wrong let me know and I&rsquo;ll fix it.  Two, Losism is not afraid to &ldquo;borrow&rdquo; from the wisdom of the universe.  If you read something here that is clearly not an original thought that&rsquo;s probably because it&rsquo;s not.  If the original source isn&rsquo;t credited and you know who it is let me know and I&rsquo;ll be more than happy to attribute credit as it is due, for Losism may be many things but vain is not one of them.</p>

<p>And now without further ado here is your first taste of the sweet sweet nectur that is Losism.</p>

<p>The only absolute truth is that no truth is absolute.  This probably the only tenant of Losism.  There is an exception to every rule and that should be considered when making all decisions.</p>

<p>To work hard at solving is probably to solve it wrong.  If you look the final solution to most software problems they are pretty damn simple. That is not say to a great deal of time is spent coming to that solution but if you find you self using all types of complex mechanations to solve a problem then its likely that will not be final solution that &ldquo;should&rdquo; be used.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
