<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Losism]]></title>
  <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-06T13:43:53-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://blakgeek.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[blakgeek]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Ma! I'm Blogging]]></title>
    <link href="http://blakgeek.github.io/blog/2014/04/06/look-mom-im-blogging/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-06T12:46:56-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://blakgeek.github.io/blog/2014/04/06/look-mom-im-blogging</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Losism aka &ldquo;The Way Of The Los&rdquo; is a philosphical, no existential, nah a spiritual way of approaching software design and development.  It comes from the mind of a guy who is neither as smart nor as hard working many others you may meet.  Losism is a living, breathing, ever evolving thing much like the its creator.</p>

<p>There are two important facts to be aware of as you embark on this journey.  One, Losism embraces typos and missing words while at the sametime relishing  the opportunity to correct them.  Translated I think faster than I type a lot of the time.  So if you see a typo, missing word or something that seems just generally wrong let me know and I&rsquo;ll fix it.  Two, Losism is not afraid to &ldquo;borrow&rdquo; from the wisdom of the universe.  If you read something here that is clearly not an original thought that&rsquo;s probably because it&rsquo;s not.  If the original source isn&rsquo;t credited and you know who it is let me know and I&rsquo;ll be more than happy to attribute credit as it is due, for Losism may be many things but vain and selfish are not in the list.</p>

<p>And now without further ado here is your first taste of the sweet sweet nectur that is Losism.</p>

<p>The only absolute truth is that no truth is absolute.  This is probably the only fixed tenant of Losism.  There is an exception to every rule and that should be considered when making all decisions in software and life.</p>

<p>To work hard at solving a problem is probably to solve it wrong.  If you look at the final solution to most problems they are pretty damn simple. That is not say to a great deal of time and thought was spent coming to that solution but if you find you self using all types of complex mechanations to solve a problem then it&rsquo;s likely you are not on track to find the final solution that &ldquo;should&rdquo; be used.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
